A Guide to the W. W. LaPrade and Brothers Records, 1803-2001 (bulk 1900-1970)
Library of Virginia
- Series VIII. Thornton L. Mullins files, 1929-1941., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 183-185b)
  - Subseries 1. Alphabetical files., 2 boxes (2 cu. ft.)
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 34)
      Mountain Road
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 35)
      Pribble and Sharpe subdivision, Hermitage Road
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 36)
      Ravenswood subdivision (Evans)
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 37)
      Ridgecrest Farms, Mrs. Myrtle Welborne subdivision
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 38-40)
      Rollingwood subdivision
    - Henrico Co. (Box 184, Folder 1)
      Rosedale subdivision B
    - Henrico Co. (Box 184, Folder 2-4)
    - Henrico Co. (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - New Kent Co. (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Newport News. (Box 184, Folder 7)
      Hilton Court
    - Newport News. (Box 184, Folder 8)
      Camp Stuart Development, Stuart Gardens, Defense Homes Corp.
    - Norfolk. (Box 184, Folder 9)
      Commodore Park subdivision
    - Orange Co. (Box 184, Folder 10)
    - Powhatan Co. (Box 184, Folder 11)
    - Prince George Co. (Box 184, Folder 12)
    - Richmond. (Box 184, Folder 13)
      Saint Christopher and Saint Catherines
    - Richmond. (Box 184, Folder 14)
      Sitterding property, Pelham Park, Fourqurean's Lane
    - Warwick Co. (Box 184, Folder 15)
      Beaconsdale Section A
    - Warwick Co. (Box 184, Folder 16)
      Beaconsdale Section B
    - Warwick Co. (Box 184, Folder 17-18)
      Beaconsdale
    - Warwick Co. (Box 184, Folder 19)
      Allen Graff property
    - Blank forms. (Box 184, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 2. Numerical files., 1 box (1 cu. ft.)
    The Numerical files were organized by a file numbering system used by Mullins. It is unclear as to what the file numbers relate. Included are surveys for Chesterfield and Henrico Counties and Richmond. It may be necessary to look at all the alphabetical and numberical files to find a specific survey.
    - 200-399. (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - 400-599. (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - 600-799. (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - 800-999. (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - 1000-1199. (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - 1200-1399. (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - 1400-1599. (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - 1600-1799. (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - 1800-1999. (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - 2000-2199. (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - 2200-2399. (Box 185, Folder 11)
    - 2400-2599. (Box 185, Folder 12)
    - 2600-2799. (Box 185, Folder 13)
    - 2800-2999. (Box 185, Folder 14)
    - 3000-3199. (Box 185, Folder 15)
    - 3200-3399. (Box 185, Folder 16)
    - 3400-3599. (Box 185, Folder 17)
    - 3600-3799. (Box 185, Folder 18)
    - 3800-3999. (Box 185, Folder 19)
    - 4000-4199. (Box 185, Folder 20)
    - 4200-4399. (Box 185, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous oversize. (Box 185a)
      Includes Chesterfield Co. (Glenwood subdivision; Coleman Wortham tract; Forest Hills; Westover) and Henrico Co. (Highland Gardens; Westham; Monument Ave. Crest; Bellevue Court; Ridgecrest Farms). Also includes Map of Varina District, Henrico County, 1933, by LaPrade.
    - Miscellaneous index cards. (Box 185b)
- Series IX. Carl Watkins files, 1945-2001., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 186-188)
  This series includes the subject files of Carl A. Watkins, Jr., chief structural engineer and partner in LaPrade. Watkins was a nephew of LaPrade and later ran the company. The files are organized alphabetically and include brochures, clippings, newsletters, and reports on a variety of topics. Topics include asphalt, dam safety, earthquakes, geological surveys, jacks, pile foundations, rock formation, and soil. Of note are several files on aviation and airplanes, including copies of the newsletter, Virginia Eagles, from the Virginia Aeronautical Historical Society, 1989-2001. Also included are copies of newsletters from the Virginia section of the American Society of Civil Engineers, 1979-1983.
  - American Society Civil Engineers. (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Aviation-Airplanes. (Box 186, Folder 2-14)
  - Aviation-Airplanes, Virginia Aeronautical Historical Society. (Box 186, Folder 15-17)
  - Aviation-Airplanes, Virginia Aeronautical Historical Society. (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - A. (Box 187, Folder 2-4)
  - B. (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - C. (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - D. (Box 187, Folder 7-8)
  - E. (Box 187, Folder 9)
  - F. (Box 187, Folder 10)
  - G. (Box 187, Folder 11-18)
  - H. (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - I. (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - J-K. (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - L. (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - M. (Box 188, Folder 5-7)
  - P. (Box 188, Folder 8-13)
  - R. (Box 188, Folder 14)
  - S. (Box 188, Folder 15-17)
  - T. (Box 188, Folder 18)
  - U-V. (Box 188, Folder 19)
  - W. (Box 188, Folder 20)
  - X-Y. (Box 188, Folder 21)
- Series X. Field Book/Diaries, 1901-2000., Extent: 156 boxes. (Box 189-344)
  The Field Books/Diaries are housed in one hundred fifty-six (156) archival boxes on shelf. Field books are arranged sequentially by book number, followed by diaries arranged chronologically. Titles from the field book covers have been transcribed into the finding aid, however, additional projects in addition to those listed on the cover may be recorded in the field book. It most cases, it seems that the most prominent projects are listed on the book cover with smaller projects simply arranged inside. Books without cover titles are labeled "various" in the finding aid. Because the field books were created simultaneously by several surveyors, their numerical order does not necessarily indicate chronological order. The approximate dates for field books was determined by scanning for the earliest and latest date recorded in the volume.
  Unnumbered books (Boxes 337-343) are organized at the end of this series. They also include field notes for more than one project. The project names from the book cover have been transcribed in the finding aid. Of note, in Box 151, is a photograph of a surveying party circa 1925. This photograph was attached to the inside cover of the book titled "Appomattox River Survey, South Property Line, Book 2." A dye-sub print of the photograph in situ has been placed in the box and the photograph has been removed from the inside cover of the volume to avoid degradation.
  Also included are time/diary books because they are directly related to the field books (Box 344). The time/diary books record the day-to-day accounts of surveyors' time and projects. In addition, the series includes an index to field books circa 1935-1966. The index, situated in the last box of this series (Box 344), is arranged chronologically and alphabetically there under.
  Arranged numerically by book number with unnumbered books organized at the end roughly by date, if discernible.
  - Book Number 1 - Notes on Portion of Brady Road, circa 1911. (Box 189)
  - Book Number 2, 6-7 - Various, 1905-1910. (Box 189)
  - Book Number 8 - Virginia Railway and Power Co., 1910-1914. (Box 189)
  - Book Number 9 - Various, circa 1910. (Box 189)
  - Book Number 10 - Henrico & Chesterfield Railway, circa 1911. (Box 189)
  - Book Number 11-12 - Various, 1910-1913. (Box 189)
  - Book Number 13-14 - Richmond College (University of Richmond), circa 1912. (Box 189)
  - Book Number 15 - Miscellaneous Notes, Washington Ward, 1911-1912. (Box 190)
  - Book Number 16 - Various, 1912. (Box 190)
  - Book Number 17 - Westmoreland Place of Sands-Patterson Associates, 1913. (Box 190)
  - Book Number 18 - Highland Park, Roselawn Corp., circa 1913. (Box 190)
  - Book Number 19 - Various, 1912-1913. (Box 190)
  - Book Number 20 - Thomas F. Jeffries, 1913. (Box 190)
  - Book Number 21 - Manchester District, 1914. (Box 190)
  - Book Number 22 - Chesterfield County, 1913-1914. (Box 190)
  - Book Number 23-24 - Henrico & Chesterfield Railway (Preliminary), circa 1911. (Box 190)
  - Book Number 25 - Weather Reports, 1909-1914. (Box 191)
  - Book Number 26 - Miscellaneous Land Surveys, 1914-1915. (Box 191)
  - Book Number 28, 30 - Virginia Railway Power Co., Locks Power Plant, 1914. (Box 191)
  - Book Number 31 - Clover Hill and Midlothian Districts, 1914. (Box 191)
  - Book Number 32 - Tidewater and Western Railroad Co., Right of Way and Track Notes, Cumberland Co., 1914. (Box 191)
  - Book Number 33 - Chesterfield County, 1914. (Box 191)
  - Book Number 34 - Matoaca District, 1914. (Box 191)
  - Book Number 35 - Miscellaneous Surveys, 1915. (Box 191)
  - Book Number 36 - Petersburg and Appomattox Railroad, 1915. (Box 192)
  - Book Number 37 - Richmond College (University of Richmond), circa 1915. (Box 192)
  - Book Number 38-39 - Misses (Mrs.) Eppes, City Point, No. 1-2, 1915. (Box 192)
  - Book Number 40 - Petersburg and Appomattox Railroad Co., 1915. (Box 192)
  - Book Number 42-43 - Various, 1916-1931. (Box 192)
  - Book Number 43A - Westview, 1916-1922. (Box 192)
  - Book Number 44-47 - Various, 1919-1920. (Box 192)
  - Book Number 48 - Imperial Tobacco Co.; Old Dominion Iron and Steel Corp., Belle Isle, 1920. (Box 193)
  - Book Number 49-55 - Various, 1920-1921. (Box 193)
  - Book Number 56 - Alleghany Warehouses, T. M. Carrington-Miller Manufacturing Co., 1921. (Box 193)
  - Book Number 57-65 - Various, 1921-1922. (Box 194)
  - Book Number 66 - Various, circa 1922. (Box 195)
  - Book Number 67 - Lucille N. Miller Notes, 1922. (Box 195)
  - Book Number 68-69 - Various, circa 1922-1923. (Box 195)
  - Book Number 70A-D - Forest Lawn Cemetery # 1-4, 1923-1924. (Box 195)
  - Book Number 70E - Forest Lawn [Cemetery] Roads, 1924. (Box 195)
  - Book Number 71A-B - Pump House # 1-2, 1923-1925. (Box 195)
  - Book Number 72 - Chesterfield Realty Corp., 1923. (Box 196)
  - Book Number 73 - Various, 1923. (Box 196)
  - Book Number 74 - David M. Lea Co., Chesterfield Co., 1923. (Box 196)
  - Book Number 75 - Various and David M. Lea Co., Chesterfield Co., 1923. (Box 196)
  - Book Number 76-78 - Various, 1923-1925. (Box 196)
  - Book Number 79 - Back Bay, 1924. (Box 196)
  - Book Number 80 - Various, 1924-1925. (Box 196)
  - Book Number 81 - Various, 1924. (Box 197)
  - Book Number 82 - Surry Lumber Co. and Various, 1924-1932. (Box 197)
  - Book Number 83-84 - Various, 1924-1926. (Box 197)
  - Book Number 85 - David M. Lea Co. and Various, 1923-1925. (Box 197)
  - Book Number 86 - Harvard Apartments and Various, 1925. (Box 197)
  - Book Number 87 - Roanoke Rapids Power Co., Roanoke Rapids, NC, 1925. (Box 197)
  - Book Number 88 - Various, 1925. (Box 197)
  - Book Number 89 - Manchester and Falling Creek Turnpike, 1925. (Box 197)
  - Book Number 90 - Various, 1924-1925. (Box 197)
  - Book Number 91 - Virginia Industrial School, Maidens, VA, 1925. (Box 198)
  - Book Number 92-92A - Woodstock Home and Land Co., Inc., 1925. (Box 198)
  - Book Number 93-99 - Various, 1925-1926. (Box 198)
  - Book Number 100 - Virginia Electric and Power Co., Fredericksburg, VA, and Various, 1926. (Box 198)
  - Book Number 101 - Various, 1926. (Box 198)
  - Book Number 102-103 - Various, 1926. (Box 199)
  - Book Number 104 - Boscobel Quarries, Etc., Aqua Vista, Westover Gardens, 1926. (Box 199)
  - Book Number 105 - Various, circa 1926. (Box 199)
  - Book Number 105A - Forrest Hill Terrace, Amphill, and Various, 1926. (Box 199)
  - Book Number 106-106C - Westclox, Book No. 1-5, 1926. (Box 199)
  - Book Number 107-108 - Various, 1926-1927. (Box 199)
  - Book Number 109 - Twohy Gravel Pit, Commonwealth Sand and Gravel Corp., and Various, 1927. (Box 200)
  - Book Number 110 - Various, 1927. (Box 200)
  - Book Number 111 - Various, 1930. (Box 200)
  - Book Number 111 - Virginia Electric and Power Co., Roanoke Rapids, 1927. (Box 200)
  - Book Number 112 - Belmont, T & W at Bermuda, and Various, 1927. (Box 200)
  - Book Number 113-116 - Various, 1927. (Box 200)
  - Book Number 117 - Belmont, Hopewell; J. K. Johnson Estate; Girl Scouts; and Various, 1927. (Box 200)
  - Book Number 118 - Holy Cross and Various, 1927. (Box 200)
  - Book Number 119 - Various, circa 1927. (Box 200)
  - Book Number 120 - Westover Gardens and Various, 1927. (Box 201)
  - Book Number 121 - Slater School Ethiopian, Lower Brandon, Prince George County, VA, circa 1927. (Box 201)
  - Book Number 122 - Brandon, circa 1927. (Box 201)
  - Book Number 122 - Various, 1935. (Box 201)
  - Book Number 123 - Amphill and Bellwood (duPont) and Various, 1927. (Box 201)
  - Book Number 124 - Woodbury Forest School, 1927. (Box 201)
  - Book Number 125-126 - Various, 1927. (Box 201)
  - Book Number 127 - Zeigler, Middleburg, VA, and Various, 1927. (Box 201)
  - Book Number 128 - William Zeigler, Noroton, CT, 1927. (Box 201)
  - Book Number 129-129A - St. Joseph, circa 1927. (Box 201)
  - Book Number 130-132 - Various, 1927-1928. (Box 202)
  - Book Number 133 - Chesterfield Hills Country Club and Various, 1928. (Box 202)
  - Book Number 134-138 - Various, 1928-1932. (Box 202)
  - Book Number 139 - Girl Scout Camp, Bon Air, and Various, 1928. (Box 202)
  - Book Number 140 - Westhampton Sewer and Richmond College, and Various, 1928. (Box 202)
  - Book Number 141 - Conn Subdivision and Various, 1928. (Box 203)
  - Book Number 142 - H. W. Ellison, H. C. Matthesson, Irvington on Hudson, and Various, 1928. (Box 203)
  - Book Number 143 - Claremont Manor and Manchester Canal, 1928. (Box 203)
  - Book Number 144 - H. C. Matthesson, Irvington on Hudson, Birdwoods (McClery), Mrs. N. F. Brady, Inesfada, 1928. (Box 203)
  - Book Number 145 - Various, 1928. (Box 203)
  - Book Number 146-146A - Woodbury Forest School and Various, 1928. (Box 203)
  - Book Number 147-147B - Blandford Cemetery, Petersburg, VA, 1928. (Box 203)
  - Book Number 148-149 - Various, 1929. (Box 203)
  - Book Number 150 - Various, 1929. (Box 204)
  - Book Number 151 - F. L. Harney, 1929. (Box 204)
  - Book Number 152-153 - Various, 1929. (Box 204)
  - Book Number 154 - Mrs. Harry Potter, 1929. (Box 204)
  - Book Number 155-156 - Sherwood Forest (Pratt's), Book 1, Sherwood Forest, Book 2; Windsor Shades; Chester- Centralia Road, 1929-1932. (Box 204)
  - Book Number 157 - Fredericksburg (Pratt) (Topography), 1929. (Box 204)
  - Book Number 158 - Fredericksburg, 1929. (Box 204)
  - Book Number 159 - Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania Co. Side) Topography, 1929. (Box 204)
  - Book Number 160-161 - Vesper, E. Wantham, National Oil, and Various, 1929. (Box 204)
  - Book Number 162-162A - Cohart, W. T. Rush, 1929. (Box 205)
  - Book Number 163-163B - Gray Lumber Co., 1929. (Box 205)
  - Book Number 164-165 - Various, 1929-1930. (Box 205)
  - Book Number 166-168 - Scaleby and Various, 1929-1932. (Box 205)
  - Book Number 169 - Sweetbriar College, 1929. (Box 205)
  - Book Number 170-172, 174 - Various, 1929-1935. (Box 206)
  - Book Number 175 - Holy Cross, 1930-1935. (Box 206)
  - Book Number 176-176B - Novitiate and Taylor, 1930. (Box 206)
  - Book Number 177 - University of Virginia Stadium, 1930. (Box 206)
  - Book Number 178 - Various, circa 1930. (Box 206)
  - Book Number 179-181 - Various, circa 1930. (Box 207)
  - Book Number 182 - State Penal Commission, Goochland Co., circa 1931. (Box 207)
  - Book Number 183 - Various,. (Box 207)
  - Book Number 185 - Mr. Giles Whiting Scarborough,. (Box 207)
  - Book Number 186-187 - Various,. (Box 207)
  - Book Number 188 - Cleveland St. and Monument Ave., 1931. (Box 207)
  - Book Number 192, 194-203 - Various, circa 1931. (Box 208)
  - Book Number 204-204A - Various, circa 1932. (Box 209)
  - Book Number 205 - Appomattox Surveys, Individual Property Lines, Northside, 1933. (Box 209)
  - Book Number 206-213 - Various, circa 1933. (Box 209)
  - Book Number 214, 217-218 - Various, circa 1934. (Box 210)
  - Book Number 219 - 2930 W. Cary St., Parcel Post Building- Richmond, 1935. (Box 210)
  - Book Number 221 - F. F. Jessup, 1935. (Box 210)
  - Book Number 222-225 - Various, circa 1935. (Box 210)
  - Book Number 226-229B, 241W-243W - Various, circa 1936. (Box 211)
  - Book Number 245W-253W - Various, circa1938. (Box 212)
  - Book Number 351, 353 - Various, circa 1940. (Box 212)
  - Book Number 354-364 - Various, circa 1940. (Box 213)
  - Book Number 365-372 - Various, circa 1937-1939. (Box 214)
  - Book Number 373-374 - Mary Baldwin- Staunton, circa 1939. (Box 214)
  - Book Number 375 - Various, circa 1938. (Box 214)
  - Book Number 376-386 - Various, circa 1940. (Box 215)
  - Book Number 387-394, 396-399 - Various, circa 1940. (Box 216)
  - Book Number 400-410 - Various, circa 1941-1942. (Box 217)
  - Book Number 411-420 - Various, circa 1943-1944. (Box 218)
  - Book Number 421 - McGuire, 1943-1944. (Box 218)
  - Book Number 422 - Various, 1944. (Box 218)
  - Book Number 422A - Various, 1944. (Box 219)
  - Book Number 423 - McGuire Park, 1944. (Box 219)
  - Book Number 424-429 - Various, 1944. (Box 219)
  - Book Number 430 - Chesterfield Court, 1944. (Box 219)
  - Book Number 432-433 - Various, 1945. (Box 219)
  - Book Number 434-443, 447 - Various, 1945. (Box 220)
  - Book Number 448-459 - Various, 1945-1946. (Box 221)
  - Book Number 460-467, 469-472 - Various, 1946. (Box 222)
  - Book Number 473, 475-486 - Various, 1946. (Box 223)
  - Book Number 487-490 - Various, 1947. (Box 224)
  - Book Number 491 - Tuckahoe Land Corp., Saylor's Creek Battlefield, H. L. Ferguson (lots), 1947. (Box 224)
  - Book Number 492-493 - Various, 1947. (Box 224)
  - Book Number 494 - Malvern Manor, 1947-1948. (Box 224)
  - Book Number 495-496 - Various, 1947. (Box 224)
  - Book Number 497-498 - Various, 1947. (Box 225)
  - Book Number 499 - C. A. Watkins, Jr. Time Log, 1947-1950. (Box 225)
  - Book Number 501-504, 506-507, 513-514 - Various, 1947-1948. (Box 225)
  - Book Number 515 - Brandy Rock Farm, 1948-1949. (Box 226)
  - Book Number 516-517, 519-524 - Various, 1948-1949. (Box 226)
  - Book Number 525-531 - Various, 1949-1950. (Box 227)
  - Book Number 532 - Brandy Rock, etc., 1949-1960. (Box 227)
  - Book Number 533 - Alten S. Miller- South Claremont, Surry Co., VA, 1948-1949. (Box 227)
  - Book Number 534 - Various, 1948. (Box 227)
  - Book Number 535-544 - Various, 1948-1949. (Box 228)
  - Book Number 545-550 - Various, 1949. (Box 229)
  - Book Number 551 - Alten S. Miller- South Claremont, Surry Co., VA; Mooreland Farms- Eugene B. West, 1949-1950. (Box 229)
  - Book Number 552-556 - Various, circa 1949-1950. (Box 229)
  - Book Number 557-566 - Various, 1949-1951. (Box 230)
  - Book Number 567 - Various, 1949-1950. (Box 231)
  - Book Number 568 - Mooreland Farms, 1949. (Box 231)
  - Book Number 569-573 - Various, 1949-1950. (Box 231)
  - Book Number 574 - Mooreland Farms, 1950. (Box 231)
  - Book Number 575-576 - Various, 1950-1951. (Box 231)
  - Book Number 577-586 - Various, 1950-1951. (Box 232)
  - Book Number 587-596 - Various, circa 1950. (Box 233)
  - Book Number 597, 599-607 - Various, 1950-1951. (Box 234)
  - Book Number 608-618 - Various, circa 1951. (Box 235)
  - Book Number 619-626 - Various, circa 1951. (Box 236)
  - Book Number 627 - Chesterfield Court, etc., 1951. (Box 236)
  - Book Number 628 - Various, circa 1951. (Box 236)
  - Book Number 629-634 - Various, circa 1951. (Box 237)
  - Book Number 635 - Quantico "As Built", 1951. (Box 237)
  - Book Number 636 - James River Lumber Co., etc., Surry Co., VA, 1951-1952. (Box 237)
  - Book Number 638-639 - Various, circa 1951. (Box 237)
  - Book Number 640-644, 646-647 - Various, 1951-1952. (Box 238)
  - Book Number 648 - Housing Project, Dahlgren, King George Co., VA, 1952. (Box 238)
  - Book Number 649-650 - Various, circa 1951-1954. (Box 238)
  - Book Number 651-653, 655 - Various, 1951-1952. (Box 239)
  - Book Number 656 - Naval Mine Depot, 1952. (Box 239)
  - Book Number 658-659 - Various, 1952. (Box 239)
  - Book Number 660 - James River Lumber Co., Surry Co., VA, 1952-1953. (Box 239)
  - Book Number 661 - Naval Mine Depot, 1952. (Box 239)
  - Book Number 662 - Various, 1952. (Box 239)
  - Book Number 663-665 - Various, 1952-1954. (Box 240)
  - Book Number 666-667 - Naval Mine Depot, 1952. (Box 240)
  - Book Number 668-672 - Various, 1952-1954. (Box 240)
  - Book Number 673-674 - Various, 1952-1953. (Box 241)
  - Book Number 675 - Fort Monroe, circa 1952. (Box 241)
  - Book Number 676-682 - Various, circa 1953. (Box 241)
  - Book Number 683-685 - Various, 1953-1954. (Box 242)
  - Book Number 686 - James River Lumber Co., 1953. (Box 242)
  - Book Number 687-689 - Various, 1953-1954. (Box 242)
  - Book Number 690 - The Texas Co., circa 1954. (Box 242)
  - Book Number 691-692 - Various, 1953. (Box 242)
  - Book Number 693 - James River Lumber Co., Surry Co., VA, 1953. (Box 243)
  - Book Number 694-702 - Various, circa 1953. (Box 243)
  - Book Number 703 - Various, 1954. (Box 244)
  - Book Number 704 - Greenbrier Hills, 1954. (Box 244)
  - Book Number 705 - James River Lumber Co., Surry Co., VA, 1953-1954. (Box 244)
  - Book Number 706-709 - Various, 1954. (Box 244)
  - Book Number 710 - D. M. Lea, 1954. (Box 244)
  - Book Number 711-712 - Various, 1954. (Box 244)
  - Book Number 713-717 - Various, 1954. (Box 245)
  - Book Number 718 - James River Lumber Co., 1954-1956. (Box 245)
  - Book Number 719-722 - Various, 1954-1955. (Box 245)
  - Book Number 723--724 - Various, 1954. (Box 246)
  - Book Number 725 - Greendale Manor, 1954. (Box 246)
  - Book Number 726-730 - Various, 1954-1956. (Box 246)
  - Book Number 731 - Various, 1954-1984. (Box 247)
  - Book Number 732 - Greenbrier Hills, 1954. (Box 247)
  - Book Number 733-738 - Various, 1954. (Box 247)
  - Book Number 739 - James River Estates, 1954-1955. (Box 247)
  - Book Number 740 - Various, 1954-1955. (Box 247)
  - Book Number 741-750 - Various, circa 1954-1955. (Box 248)
  - Book Number 751-752 - Westbourne, 1955. (Box 249)
  - Book Number 753 - Various, 1955. (Box 249)
  - Book Number 754 - Central Gardens, circa 1955. (Box 249)
  - Book Number 755 - Fort Belvior, circa 1955. (Box 249)
  - Book Number 756 - Various, circa 1955. (Box 249)
  - Book Number 757 - Fort Belvior, 1955. (Box 249)
  - Book Number 758 - Various, 1955-1957. (Box 249)
  - Book Number 759-760 - Fort Belvior, 1955-1956. (Box 249)
  - Book Number 761-767 - Various, 1955-1956. (Box 250)
  - Book Number 768 - Westbourne, circa 1956. (Box 250)
  - Book Number 769 - Central Gardens, circa 1955. (Box 250)
  - Book Number 770 - Various, 1955. (Box 250)
  - Book Number 771-772 - Various, 1955-1956. (Box 251)
  - Book Number 773-774 - Westbourne, 1955-1956. (Box 251)
  - Book Number 775-776, 778 - Various, 1955-1956. (Box 251)
  - Book Number 779 - Central Gardens, 1955. (Box 251)
  - Book Number 780-781 - Various, 1955-1956. (Box 251)
  - Book Number 782 - Various, 1955-1958. (Box 252)
  - Book Number 783 - Westgate, 1955. (Box 252)
  - Book Number 784-791 - Various, 1955-1960. (Box 252)
  - Book Number 792 - Various, 1955-1956. (Box 253)
  - Book Number 793 - Repine, 1955-1959. (Box 253)
  - Book Number 794-795, 797-798 - Various, circa 1955-1959. (Box 253)
  - Book Number 799 - Roxbury, 1955-1956. (Box 253)
  - Book Number 800 - Southside Plaza, 1956. (Box 253)
  - Book Number 801-803 - Various, 1955-1958. (Box 253)
  - Book Number 804 - Repine, 1955-1959. (Box 253)
  - Book Number 805-812 - Various, circa 1956. (Box 254)
  - Book Number 813 - Pocoshock Heights, 1956-1957. (Box 254)
  - Book Number 814-816 - Various, 1956. (Box 254)
  - Book Number 817-818 - D. M. Lea, 1956. (Box 255)
  - Book Number 819-825, 827 - Various, 1956-1960. (Box 255)
  - Book Number 828 - Prestwould Farms, 1956-1960. (Box 255)
  - Book Number 829 - Various, 1956-1958. (Box 255)
  - Book Number 830-835 - Various, 1957-1962. (Box 256)
  - Book Number 836 - E. Carlton Wilton (Guza Tract), Patterson Hills (Boundary, Topo, Levels), 1956-1960. (Box 256)
  - Book Number 838-842 - Various, 1956-1960. (Box 256)
  - Book Number 843-846, 848-854 - Various, 1956-1968. (Box 257)
  - Book Number 855 - Freeman Heights, 1959. (Box 257)
  - Book Number 856-857 - Various, 1956-1959. (Box 258)
  - Book Number 858 - Hanover Farms, 1956-1959. (Box 258)